<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Houses>
  <house>
    <title>Griffindor</title>
    <texbox>Our emblem is the lion, the bravest of all creatures; our house colours are scarlet and gold, and our common room lies up in Gryffindor Tower.
This is, quite simply, the best house at Hogwarts. It's where the bravest and boldest end up – for instance: Albus Dumbledore! Yes, Dumbledore himself,
 the greatest wizard of our time, was a Gryffindor! If that's not enough for you, 
I don’t know what it is.
I won't keep you long, as all you need to do to find out more about your house is to follow Harry Potter and his friends as I lead them up to their dormitories.
 Enjoy your time at Hogwarts – but how could you fail to? You've become part of the best house in the school. </texbox>
  
  </house>

  <house>
    <title>Slytherin</title>
    <texbox>Our emblem is the serpent, the wisest of creatures; our house colours are emerald green and silver,
     and our common room lies behind a concealed entrance down in the dungeons. 
     As you'll see, its windows look out into the depths of the Hogwarts lake. 
     We often see the giant squid swooshing by – and sometimes more interesting creatures.
      We like to feel that our hangout has the aura of a mysterious, underwater shipwreck.
      Firstly, let's dispel a few myths. You might have heard rumours about Slytherin house – that we're all into the Dark Arts, 
      and will only talk to you if your great-grandfather was a famous wizard, and rubbish like that. Well, you don't want to believe everything you hear from competing houses.
       I'm not denying that we've produced our share of Dark wizards, but so have the other three houses – they just don't like admitting it.
        And yes, we have traditionally tended to take students who come from long lines of witches and wizards,
         but nowadays you'll find plenty of people in Slytherin house who have at least one Muggle parent. </texbox>
  </house>

  <house>
    <title>Hufflepuff</title>
    <texbox>Our emblem is the badger, an animal that is often underestimated, 
    because it lives quietly until attacked, but which, when provoked, can fight off animals much larger than itself, including wolves.
     Our house colours are yellow and black, and our common room lies one floor below the ground, on the same corridor as the kitchens.
     Hufflepuffs are trustworthy and loyal. We don't shoot our mouths off, but cross us at your peril; like our emblem, the badger,
      we will protect ourselves, our friends and our families against all-comers. Nobody intimidates us. </texbox>
  </house>

  <house>
    <title>Ravenclaw</title>
    <texbox>Our emblem is the eagle, which soars where others cannot climb; our house colours are blue and bronze,
     and our common room is found at the top of Ravenclaw Tower, behind a door with an enchanted knocker. 
     The arched windows set into the walls of our circular common room look down at the school grounds: the lake, the Forbidden Forest, 
     the Quidditch pitch and the Herbology gardens. No other house in the school has such stunning views.
     Without wishing to boast, this is the house where the cleverest witches and wizards live. Our founder, 
     Rowena Ravenclaw, prized learning above all else – and so do we. Unlike the other houses, who all have concealed entrances to their common rooms,
      we don't need one. The door to our common room lies at the top of a tall, winding staircase. It has no handle, 
      but an enchanted bronze knocker in the shape of an eagle. When you rap on the door, this knocker will ask you a question,
       and if you can answer it correctly, you are allowed in. This simple barrier has kept out everyone but Ravenclaws for nearly a thousand years. </texbox>
    </house>

</Houses>
